safexpress.com 2018-04-04

# Privacy Policy

                                         Privacy Policy
Safexpress Private Limited understands the importance of protecting the privacy of the
users of Safexpress’ website (www.safexpress.com). Safexpress’ privacy policy gives
information about its practices to customer privacy and information security.
The information collected on the website is used to market and improve the services of
Safexpress and its Group Companies’, to improve the content and services on the
Safexpress’ website and make it easier to use and more appropriate to individual users and
to contact its users with updates to the website or for other marketing purposes.
In general, you can visit the website without telling us who you are or revealing any
information about yourself. Our web servers temporarily save the information provided by
you for security purposes, the connection data of the computer connecting to our site, a list
of links that you visit within our site, the date and duration of your visit, the identification
data of the type of browser and operating system used.
Safexpress’ website currently provides access to its users regarding Shipment Tracking,
Pickup Request, Services Offered, Pin codes Served, Network Details, Dedicated Customer
Portal for Billing, POD, Shipment Report and Other Details. In future, Safexpress may add
other features to enhance the customers’ experience.
Scope of Privacy Policy & Its Applicability
This Privacy Policy applies to Safexpress, Group Companies, associates, workers, staff and
colleagues who gather, have, use, process, record, store, exchange, reveal, handle, transfer
and get information from you and third party including yet not restricted to any specialists,
temporary workers, counselors, bookkeepers, accountants, operators, agents,
representatives of www.safexpress.com and/or service suppliers and so on who give
administrations to or for www.safexpress.com's benefit regarding its business ("Third
Party"). This Policy abridges what sort of Information (as characterized hereinafter) we
gather about you, reason for accumulation, storing and use of such Information, to whom
such Information might be transferred/disclosed and how we keep your privacy safe and
secure.
Safexpress’ Privacy Policy is liable to change whenever without prior notification. To
ensure you know about any changes or updates, please review this policy page
occasionally. By visiting the website, you consent to be bound by the terms and conditions
of this Privacy Policy. In the event that you don't concur, kindly don't use or visit our
website. By negligible use of the website, you explicitly agree to reveal your Information as
per this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of
Use.

Collection of Information and Its Usage
Safexpress may collect personal information from you including your first and last name,
contact number, email id, complete address and any other information, when you
knowingly provide us with this information. We shall not retain any information for longer
than it is required.
Usually, we require this information for the following purposes:
       To understand your needs and provide you with the more customized services
       To improve the content and services on the Safexpress’ website and make it easier
        to use and more appropriate to its users
       To contact its users with updates to the website or for other marketing purposes
       To bill customers for the services they elect to use
We do not share, sell, transfer or disclose your personal data to any other organization or
third party and will not do so in future, unless required by law or for the purpose of
contract or you have given express consent to do so.
Certain areas of the website, including but not limited to “Customer Portal”, “Tracking”
require registration id or tracking id for access. Information obtained from registered users
may also be used only for Safexpress marketing purposes.
Security of Information
This website is developed on Oracle ADF which runs on Web Logic server and uses AIX
operating system which is very safe and secure. Also, we have taken reasonable steps to
protect the ‘loss’, ‘misuse’ or ‘alteration’ of information collected. The data collected from
the users resides behind a firewall with access restricted to authorize personnel based on
their requirement for the data to provide efficient services to customers. We also maintain
high level of confidentiality for the information collected.
Keeping your payment information secure
Safexpress protects your personal information, transaction data, credit, debit & prepaid
card and internet banking information with industry-leading security.
Using our website or App for payments is easy, secure, and private. It’s simple for you, and
it’s built with integrated security in both hardware and software, making it a safer way to
pay than with your credit, debit & prepaid card and internet banking.
It has been designed to protect your personal information. To securely transmit your
payment information when you pay in app and website, Safexpress receives your
encrypted transaction and re-encrypts it with a developer-specific key before the
transaction information is sent to the developer or payment processor. This key helps
ensure that only the app or website you’re purchasing from can access your encrypted
payment information. Safexpress doesn't collect any transaction information that can be

tied back to you. Payment transactions are between you, the merchant (or developer for
payments made within app and website), and your bank only.
Functionality of Cookies
Cookies are small files that websites put on your PC to store information about your
preferences. Cookies can improve your browsing experience by allowing sites to
remember your preferences or letting you avoid signing in each time you visit certain sites.
Cookies can help Safexpress to save the images of our Logistic Parks, content, fleet etc. It
also helps us to save users data so that the website “remember and auto fill” the user ID
when they login again on the website as and when required. Also, It ask the users who login
on the customer portal to save the password by clicking on “remember the password” for
future use if they are want to do so.
Log Files
Safexpress website uses log files to capture date and time of visit, referring address
(location from which a visitor comes to the Safexpress website), type of Internet browser,
and visitor's IP address.
Link to Other Sites
Safexpress website doesn’t contain links that connects to other websites. It only contains
the link of its sister concern – Safeducate. Users using that link should consult the privacy
policy of that website before using the services on that site to determine how the user’s
information may be used.
Contacting the website administrators
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your
dealings with this Web site, you can contact-
CORPORATE OFFICE
Safexpress Pvt. Ltd.,
NH 8, Mahipalpur Extension,
New Delhi - 110 037, India.
Contact No.: 1800 113 113 (Toll Free)
Email – info@safexpress.com
